Russian e increased by a quarter, that
русского э на четверть увеличилось то
is, for example, 100 million Russians became
есть было например русских 100 млн стало
plus
плюс
Hello Hello, I’m from the city of
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте я из города
Khmelnitsky Where are you from the city of
Хмельницкий Вы откуда город
Omsk Omsk understood yes
Омск Омск понял да
Siberia Western Siberia understood what
Сибирь Западная Сибирь понял о чём
you are talking about from Omsk Yes, I just came to
общаетесь из Омска Да просто зашёл
talk about what Yes on various topics
поговорить о чём Да на разные темы
Suggest For what  To different I’m saying
Предлагайте На какие На разные Говорю же
no, I
нет определённый те
understand that I understand, I’m talking about the topic of the demographic
понял я общаюсь о теме демографического
crisis in the Russian
кризиса в Российской
Federation, what is it, say
Федерации в чём он заключается скажи
the Russians are dying out, yes, I wouldn’t say, and
руские вымирают да я бы не сказал да и
more and more
всё больше стаёт
immigrants are coming. Well, there is a problem of migration in Russia,
приезжих Ну проблема миграции в России
accordingly, and besides, there are Russians
она есть соответственно Да ещё и русские
there too  that they die naturally, and they also
там мало того что природно умирают Да ещ
die unnaturally in a non-native
и не природно умирают неродным
way. Well, I don’t agree with you
способом Ну то что я не согласен с Вами
that Russians are dying, and so on, how
что русский умирает и так далее ну как
can you disagree with me? Do
вы вы можете не со мной не соглашаться У
you have Rosstat, which publishes
вас есть росстат который публикует
demographic data? Yes you can. For what
демографические данные Да можеш За какой
year? Please tell me  for the previous one for
год Скажите пожалуйста за предыдущий за
2 Okay, let's go, let me google it, I allow
2 Хорошо давай можно давайте я загуглю
you I didn't ask permission
разрешаю вам Я не спрашивал разрешения
So you say, let me google it, you
Так вы сказать давайте я загуглю вы
asked, I let me google it, and you're
спросили Я давайте я загуглю а вы
making excuses, you yourself just
оправдываете вы сами только что
confirmed that you're making excuses like that, you're
подтвердили Что вы так оправдываете
nervous, I'm not making excuses in any
нервничаете я не оправдываюсь ни в коем
case, what?  you are justifying that you are not
случае А что вы оправдываете что вы не
justifying I am not
оправдываете я не
making excuses making excuses Yes,
оправдываюсь оправдывается
you are still googling now and you are not googling
Да ты сейчас ещё гуглишь и не на гуглишь
in any way
по-любому
I noticed something that most Russians
Я что-то заметил у большинство россиян
Kato have a problem with finding information
Като проблема с поиском информации Да
No, I went in I Well, I found the information now I
нет я зашёл я Ну нашл информацию сейчас
am looking where exactly by
смотрю где именно по
nationality I  I just see
национальностям Я просто вижу
the birth rate by subject, and so
рождаемость по субъектом и так
on. Well, what are you telling me?
далее Ну что вы мне
27% of the Russian population in 202 alone is not a
27% русского населения только за за 202
bad
год неплоха
increase in the Russian population. That is, you
прирост именно русского То есть ты
want to say that the Russian population has increased by a quarter,
хочешь сказать русского на четверть
that is, for example, there were
увеличилась то есть было например
100 million Russians, now it’s plus
русских 100 млн стало плюс
25 No, I’m saying 27 from  birth rate,
25 Нет я говорю 27 от рождаемости ещё
look again what
раз смотри что
is birth rate, what is
такое
birth rate, that is, we
отж что от рождаемость что то есть у нас
get, roughly
получается грубо
speaking, 100% 27 of these are Russians, where do you see this, were born Well, that is, were born,
говоря 100% 27 из это русские где ты
look, out of 100 born, 27 are only
смотри из 100 рождённых 27 только
Russians Well, well, well, but there are Russians in
русских Да ну и ну так а русских же в
Russia  more than half is true And
России больше половины правда А рожает
less than half give birth Why not wait
меньше половины Почему нет подождите
wait look demographically it
подождите смотрите демографическое она
doesn’t consist of the fact that we also have a birth rate
не складывается из того что рождаемости
naturally you again you said you
естественно ты ещё раз ты сказал ты
said that out of 100 people born 27 are Russians you said
сказал что из 100 рождённых 27 русских
We have we have 27% this  here, but
У нас имее у нас имеется 27% это вот но
also a part is still made up of the small peoples of
также часть ещё составляет малые народы
Russia; firstly, these are also Avars and
России это во-первых это также аварцы и
so on, Yakuts Babur and so on. Which,
так далее якуты Бабур и так далее Что
accordingly, does not mean that they are not
соответственно не говорит то что они не
Russian. Well, how can they be non-Russian? The
русские Ну как они могут быть нерусскими
EU is born Russia. In the sense of
ЕС рождаются Росси В смысле
non-Russian, everything where you
нерус все куда ты
ran off
убежал
to now  the type let himself go like that Damn, I’m
сечас тип так попустил сам себя Блин я
Nekha 27% that 27% of 100% born 27%
Неха 27% что 27% из 100% рождённый 27%
Russian I don’t know where he dug it up
русский я не знаю где он это откопал
like yes he himself said such a thing that it’s just In
типа да он сам сказал такую ю что просто
short, the Beshka himself didn’t know how to escape and
Короче сам бешка не знал как убежать и
ran away
убежал
Well, the Yakuts were hardly born there  everything Well, what are they
Ну родились якуты там вряд всё Ну они
Russians writing on my Telegram directly at once axis VN
русские пись на мий Telegram прямо зараз
apok tse more and more respectfully YouTube taking
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through the skarg ODS in your ban and even
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
more videos are not showing to people at all times
багато видео не показуе людям вчасно не
information about streams is for this
показуе информация про стримы тому для
purpose we are Mali operational link
того щоб мы Мали оперативный звязок
write directly at once and Popik there in
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
telegram okrim video sche tezh tsikava and
телеграми окрим видео ще теж цикава и
korisna information and we are responsible for you trimati
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
postiyny operational link
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava ukraini
YouTube Слава украини
write
пиши